http://www.nasafcu.com/online-privacy-security-policy

Keeping Your Information Safe and Secure
Online Privacy & Security PolicyAs a NASA Federal Credit Union member, your privacy and security always come first. For more than 60 years we have been dedicated to member safety and protection. Find out how we protect you and how you can protect yourself by recognizing, preventing,
and reporting fraudulent activity. This Online Privacy & Security Policy (“Policy”) describes how we collect and use information related to our website. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time and in any manner, without
prior notice.We are dedicated to protecting your personal information and maintaining your trust in us. Select the following to view our Privacy Notices:  Privacy Policy Notice California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) Online Privacy Policy - While our privacy policies are the same whether you are online or not, we have extra measures in place to protect your privacy when you bank online with NASA Federal Credit Union.WebsiteOnline BankingCookiesThird Party Service ChecksOnline FormsEmail CommunicationLinkingOpt-Out Resources - Reduce the amount of advertising you receive from companies outside NASA Federal Credit Union by contacting the following agencies:Direct Mail from outside sourcesNational Credit Reporting AgenciesNational Do-Not Call RegistryWebsite PrivacyAs a general policy, we do not automatically collect personal information from our website users. We do collect and store information on the domain used to access our website, the Internet address of the website from which a user links to the Credit Union's
website and the date and time of the visit to our website. This information is used only to measure the number of visitors to our website and the route a user travels while within the Credit Union's website to better serve users in improved design
and site navigation.Online BankingPersonal identification, such as your account number and password, is collected when a valid Credit Union member with active Credit Union account(s) enters the secure online banking area of the Credit Union's website. This information enables the Credit
Union to regulate access of this information to those who request such access and those entitled to perform transactions on these account(s).
CookiesOur website may use cookies (small pieces of information sent by our web server to a visitor's web browser that reminds our site about the user the next time he or she visits). We do not store confidential or sensitive information in cookies. We use cookies
only to enhance a member's online banking session and ease navigation through our website.For certain applications, such as online banking, cookies are required to help protect the privacy of a member's transactions by, for example, automatically terminating the online session if the member forgets to log out (also see "Third Party Service
Checks" below). Cookies cannot be used to capture a user's email address, obtain data from the user's hard drive or gain confidential or sensitive information about the user. Additionally, cookies cannot be read by a website other than the one that
set the cookie. Some websites, however, use cookies to obtain information from the user's browser. The user has the option to set his or her browser to notify before accepting a cookie to control whether a cookie is accepted or rejected.It's important to note that the information we use about you helps us provide you with products, services and experiences that benefit you. You have the ability to control how your non-personal information is collected and used online.Some websites may belong to ad networks that use your browsing history across websites to choose which ads to display on their sites; the displayed ads may include advertising for NASA FCU. To learn more, and to opt out of seeing interest-based advertisements
on these sites, visit the Network Advertising Initiative home page. Please note that even if you choose to remove your information (opt out), you will still see advertisements while
you're browsing online. However the advertisements you see may be less relevant to you and your interests.Third Party Service ChecksTo protect you, we may use tools and services provided by third-parties to help us decide whether to accept submissions from personal computers, mobile phones, or other devices. These third-party providers may check whether user devices have been identified
with fraudulent or abusive transactions in the past, such as reported instances of identity theft, account takeovers, or malware attacks. For this purpose, a cookie, flash storage token, or other code file may be placed on your device to identify
it in the future when you visit our website or connect with our other online applications. If you set your browser or device to reject these cookies or tokens, you may not be able to access some features of our website or other online applications.When you access our website or other online applications, we will transmit this third-party device identification code to the third-party provider, along with data concerning certain technical attributes of your device such as the model, operating system,
and browser version, as well as the IP address (all of which are used to confirm device identification). We may then receive information from these third-party providers indicating that submissions from a user’s device should not be accepted.
We may also inform such third-party providers if we determine that a device has been used in connection with a fraudulent or abusive transaction with us. In addition, in certain situations, we may share with one or more of these third-party providers
certain personal identifying information and information about the device you are using. If your receive a message from us indicating that a requested submission has not been processed, we will provide appropriate customer service contact information.Online FormsNASA Federal Credit Union provides several online forms (for example, loan application or check order) to better serve the
needs of members. Personal information provided via any Credit Union online form is used only to process the member's request for service. These forms are transmitted via secured means. However, if the user is concerned about the security of transmitting
this information via the Internet, the member is encouraged to contact the Credit Union directly at 1-301-249-1800 or 1-888-NASA-FCU (627-2328) to transmit the information another way.Email CommunicationWe may use personal information you transmit to us to respond to inquiries for service or information, or improve the service the Credit Union provides. Since email communication may not be secure against interception by unauthorized individuals,
users may want to seek alternatives to email when it is necessary to provide sensitive or personal information.NASA Federal Credit Union will not transmit sensitive or personal information that can compromise or violate a user's privacy when communicating via email.LinkingA link to a linked website (“Linked Site”) on this website does not mean that we endorse or accept any responsibility for the content, functioning or use of such Linked Site, and you enter any such website at your own risk. You agree
that we have no control over or liability for information on Linked Sites. You should be aware that Linked Sites may contain rules and regulations, privacy provisions, confidentiality provisions, and other provisions that are different from
the provisions provided on this website. We are not responsible for such provisions, and expressly disclaim any and all liability related to such provisions. We prohibit unauthorized hypertext links to this website, or the framing of this
website.
Reducing Direct Marketing From Other SourcesDirect Marketing Association, Inc.1120 Avenue of the AmericasNew York, NY 10036212-768-7277, ext. 1500You can also remove your name from these lists by visiting the DMA consumer assistance site at dmachoice.org.National Consumer Credit Reporting AgenciesIf you would like your name removed from lists for pre-approved offers of credit or insurance obtained from the major credit reporting agencies, go to optoutprescreen.com or call
1-888-5OPTOUT (567-8688).
The information you provide is confidential and will only be used to process your request.National Do Not Call RegistryHelp eliminate unwanted and uninvited calls from telemarketers to your home when you register your telephone numbers – at no cost – with the National Do Not Call Registry.Register your residential and cell phone numbers online at donotcall.gov or by calling 1-888-382-1222. While this will stop most calls, you may still
receive calls from businesses with which you have a business relationship.For More InformationIf you have any comments, concerns or questions regarding this Policy, please contact us at 1-888-NASA-FCU (627-2328).
We’re here to helpPhone Number1-888-NASA-FCU 1 8 8 8 6 2 7 2 3 2 8Email UsLet's Chat Now
Privacy & Security Policy
Mortgages & Equity
Mortgages
Home Equity
Auto Loans
Auto Loans
Recreational Vehicles
Credit Cards
Subscribe
Your savings federally insured to at least $250,000 and backed by the full faith & credit of the U.S. Government. NMLS #486583.
©
NASA Federal Credit Union
SitemapPrivacy & SecurityTerms & Conditions
Confidential information such as account numbers and social security numbers should not be sent by email for security reasons. Instead, please contact us directly at 1-888-NASA-FCU, send us a secure message through eBranch Online Banking or Mobile
Banking, or visit your nearest branch.
You are now leaving nasafcu.com and entering a third party website that is not part of NASA Federal Credit Union.The content you are about to view is produced by a third party unaffiliated to NASA Federal Credit Union. NASA Federal takes no responsibility for the content of the page.
× Email Disclaimer
Continue Cancel
× Leaving NASA Federal
Continue Cancel
